articlesamurai.com 2017-12-27

# Noble Samurai - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

At Noble Samurai, we go to great lengths to keep your privacy just that - private. In our endeavor to provide you with helpful information and services, we will from time to time, require select elements of personal information to be submitted. This policy is designed to keep you informed about the types of information collected and how we use that information in manner that is respectful of your privacy.

When you visit or sign up to the Noble Samurai or Market Samurai site, make a purchase from one of our sites, provide us with feedback, comments or contact us in any way, we receive information that may be personally identifiable. The information that is collected from any of these actions is used in different ways, whether to contact you regarding an enquiry, to provide requested information, responding to support emails or help requests and the collection of specific web-site usage statistics and other related actions.

Where applicable, this information is also necessary to respond or send notification to you, to provide you with information that you have requested, to provide you with products or services that you have purchased, to respond to your requests regarding information and products, to contact you regarding other Noble Samurai products and services, and to contact you regarding your membership to any one of our sites.

We will not sell, barter, distribute, broadcast your personally identifiable information with any third party, unless we have your permission, or are compelled to do at the request of appropriate legal authorities.

From time-to-time, it is necessary for us to provide your information to third parties to perform services on our behalf (e.g. customer service tasks, shipping or fulfillment of products or provision of services necessary to complete a purchase that you have made, providing technical support, or in the tracking of web stats). In these, and other similar situations, it may be necessary for us to disclose relevant and personally identifiable information about you to these third parties as part of a required provision of necessary services. In all cases, we require that all information is kept confidential, only to be used for necessary purposes that arise as a direct consequence of their provision of services to us.

Cookies are utilized on the Noble Samurai and Market Samurai sites to temporarily store and access personally identifiable information on your computer. This has been implemented to increase the functionality and ease of use of these web sites. Cookies assist managing custom settings and display of tailored information, depending on the users requirements. They also provide advertising and assist us with customizing other parts of the web site to specific user needs. Temporary session variables are also stored on your computer to assist in these and similar purposes.

Over time we will also provide links and referrals to sites other than Noble Samurai, Market Samurai and its subsidiaries. Noble Samurai has no control over the content and practices of these sites and does not take any responsibility for any of their actions or results arising from using their information and/or software. Noble Samurai encourages users to read the privacy policies of referred sites if the user is in any doubt.

Noble Samurai may amend this privacy policy at any time without notice. As such, it is your responsibility to check this page for any notices of change.

We are committed to protecting your privacy.
